Finding Aid for the Phyllis Diller papers, 1934-2011 LSC.1893
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995-2002
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Includes Orange Coast College in Costa Mesa, CA; "You Don't Know Jack" voiceover work; The Cancer League Christmas Luncheon Extravaganza (honoring Diller) in Houston, TX; Exhibition at Art Spectrum Gallery in N. Miami Beach, FL; "Rosie O' Donnell Show" TV series in New York, NY; "Emily of New Moon" TV series in Prince Edward Island, Canada; "60 Minutes" TV series in Los Angeles, CA
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Includes "Emily of New Moon" TV series contract; telephone messages; Lake of the Torches in Rhinelander, WI; "Soap Opera Update" phone interview; Joan Rivers Biography TV Program on CBS; KSTP St. Paul Minneapolis Radio Talk Show interview; Pearl S. Buck Volunteer Association Cookbook.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Duplicate itineraries from 1994. Original itineraries and job folders from 1994 are not currently present in the collection. The duplicate itinerary files in folders 26 and 27 mostly correspond to original job folders in folders 1-24.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Duplicate itineraries from 1995. Original itineraries can, for the most part, be found in folders 1-9.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Duplicate itineraries from 1996. Original itineraries can, for the most part, be found in folders 10-24.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Includes Minneapolis Women's Expo; Central Missouri State University; "60 Minutes" TV series interview; 30th Anniversary of Caesar's Palace in Las Vegas, NV; Riverside Theater in Vero Beach, FL
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Includes Museum of Television and Radio honoring Jack Paar in New York, NY; Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Reno, NV; "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV series contract in Los Angeles, CA; contract for Disney film "A Bug's Life" (titled "Bugs") in Los Angeles, CA; temporary itinerary for 1997
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Includes art show in Wichita, KS; Rickman Auditorium in Arnold, MI.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    The Movies of Bob Hope marathon on AMC television channel (hosted by Diller) in Los Angeles, CA; Art Show at MGM Grand Hotel in Las Vegas, NV; Diller's Anatomical Gift Uniform Donor Card; Sheraton Hotel & Towers in Seattle, WA; Soldiers.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Includes Sailors, & Airmen's Military Ball in New York, NY; Northern California tour and publicity schedules.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Includes L'Impressionniste Barge Burgundy & Provence Cruise (departs in Paris, France); Mothers Against Sexual Abuse, Protect the Children "Guardian Angel Awards" in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Includes "A Bug's Life" film by The Walt Disney Company in Los Angeles, CA; Norris Theatre in Rolling Hills Estates, CA; Women's Expo in Madison, WI; "Emily of New Moon" TV series in Prince Edward Islands, Canada; Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Reno, NV; Friar's Club Roast and Toast Tribute to Diller; Chumash Casino in Santa Ynez, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Includes "World of Wonder" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "A Bug's Life" film by The Walt Disney Company in Los Angeles, CA; The Orleans Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas, NV; LIFE's Presidential Unsung Hero Awards in Washington, DC; The Sarasota Opera House in Sarasota, FL; November 1997 itinerary.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Includes Imperial Theatre in St. John, New Brunswick, Canada; Orleans Hotel & Casino in Las Vegas, NV; Riverside Resort in Laughlin, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Includes "Emily of New Moon" TV series in Prince Edward Islands, Canada; Art Shows at Ambassador Galleries in New York, NY and Palm Beach, FL; Art Show at Celebrity Art in Exton, PA; Black and White Charity Ball at Nevada Dance Hall Theatre in Las Vegas, NV; "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV series in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    "Animaniacs" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; Benefit for Joslyn Senior Center at Desert Island Country Club in Palm Desert, CA; "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; Peppermill Hotel & Casino in Reno, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Includes Peppermill Hotel & Casino in Reno, NV; "Denise" TV series in Pyrmont, New South Wales; Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Lake Tahoe, CA; 1998 itinerary; Drury Lane Theater in Evergreen Park, IL; Cactus Pete's in Jackpot, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Includes Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Reno, NV; Harrah's Hotel and Casino in Vicksburg, MS; "The Conan O' Brien Show" TV series in New York, NY; "A Bug's Life" film publicity in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Includes Famous Poets International at The Disneyland Hotel in Anaheim, CA; Casino Magic in Bossier, LA; Don Laughlin's Riverside Resort Hotel and Casino in Laughlin, NV; The Wyndham Hotel Toledo in Goodwill, Toledo, OH.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Includes Bakersfield Business & Finance Conference in Bakersfield, CA; Owens Illinois Theatre in Toledo, OH; "Hey Arnold" TV series in Burbank, CA; "Movie Lounge" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; LIFE (Leaders in Furthering Education)'s Presidential Unsung Hero Award Gala for Disabled American Veterans in Arlington, VA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Includes Port Huron Town Hall in Port Huron, MI; LIFE (Leaders in Furthering Education) Stardancer Gala in Manalapan, FL; VisionQuest Illinois Council for the Blind Event in Springfield, IL; Van Wezel Auditorium in Sarasota, FL.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Includes Van Wezel Auditorium in Sarasota, FL; Paper Mill Playhouse in Millburn, N.J.; Paramount Theater for the Performing Arts in Austin, TX.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Includes "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "The Jungle Book 2" film in Los Angeles, CA; Mentor High School in Mentor, OH; Ohio Northern University in Ada, OH.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Includes Sanderson Centre for the Performing Arts in Brantford, Ontario, Canada; The Rodeo Room at The Beverly Hills Hotel in Los Angeles, CA; "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; Texas Symphony in Corpus Christi, TX; "Joke's on Us week" wraparound segments on The Nashville Network in Nashville, TN.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Includes Art Show at Ambassador Galleries in New York, NY; Premiere Video Magazine "Focus on Video" Trade Show in Toronto, Canada; Spirit Lake Casino in Devil's Lake, North Dakota; "Bel Air" film in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Includes Cactus Pete's in Jackpot, NV; Marshalls' Women in Comedy Festival in New York, NY; Riverside Resort Hotel & Casino in Laughlin, NV; "When I Was Short" TV pilot in Los Angeles, CA
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Includes L.I.F.E. Art Reception in Palm Beach, FL; "Hollywood Off-Ramp" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "The New Adventures of A.R.K.-Animal Rescue Kids" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; Southwestern Ball in Dallas, TX.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Includes Veterans of Comedy Wars in San Francisco, CA; River Centre in St. Paul, MN; Stardust Hotel in Las Vegas, NV; Fairmont Hotel in San Francisco, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Includes Stardust Hotel in Las Vegas, NV; Fairmont Hotel in San Francisco, CA; itinerary for 2000; Bally's Las Vegas Casino in Las Vegas, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Includes Family Album Campaign TV promotion in Los Angeles, CA; Voltaire Restaurant and Cabaret in Chicago, IL; Treasure Chest Casino in Kenner, LA; Gay Pride in Kansas City, MO and Philadelphia, PA; Ohio Cancer Research Associates in Columbus, OH.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    BBC documentary on plastic surgery; "The Last Laugh" TV series in Toronto, Ontario; "The Bold and the Beautiful" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "Celebrity Pets" TV program in Ottawa, Ontario; "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz" theatrical show in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Includes Casino Magic in Bay St. Louis, MI; Leisure World in Laguna Woods, CA; "The Muscular Dystrophy Telethon" TV program in Los Angeles, CA; The Women in Film "LUCY" Awards in Los Angeles, CA; Suncoast Hotel & Casino in Las Vegas, NV; Riverside Resort Hotel & Casino in Laughlin, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Includes Ladies Hospital Aid Society of Western PA in Oakland, PA; The Improvisation in West Hollywood, CA; L.I.F.E. Lady in Red Gala in Palm Beach, FL; "Stories in the Air" radio broadcast in Tallahassee, FL.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Includes Orpheum Theater in Phoenix, AZ; Van Wezel Performing Arts Center in Sarasota, FL; Friars Club Honors Diller in Los Angeles, CA; Del Webb Resort in Palm Desert, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Includes Soaring Eagle Casino and Resort in Mt. Pleasant, MI; Pete 'n Keely in New York, NY; "Arliss" TV series in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Includes Pennsylvania Industries for the Blind & Handicapped in New York, NY; tour of Canada.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Includes "Titus" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "Hollywood Squares" slot machine in Las Vegas, NV; Grand Casino in Biloxi, MS; 2001 itinerary; Suncoast Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Includes publicity report for Diller's engagement at Living Arts Centre in Mississauga, Ontario.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Includes "Celebrities Take a Stand" TV series; Gila River Casino in Chandler, AZ; M.Y. Dream Seeker Mediterranean Cruise.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Includes Children's Charity Gala in Houston, TX; Riverside Resort in Laughlin, NV; Mystic Lake Casino in Prior Lake, MN; "Titus" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; Suncoast Hotel and Casino in Las Vegas, NV.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Includes "Dear Sheldon" theatrical play, tour.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Includes "TV Guide" photo shoot in Los Angeles, CA; private party in Palm Beach, FL; Mohegan Sun Resort in Uncasville, CT; Grand Casino in Hinckley, MN.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Includes Bob Hope Museum Exhibition at United States Air force Museum in Dayton, OH; "The Drew Carey Show" TV series; "BBC Stand Up America" TV series in Los Angeles, CA; "The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron, Boy Genius" TV series in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folder and Other Activities, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Includes River Raisin Center for the Arts in Monroe, MI; The Ritz Theatre in Tiffin, OH; "The Sally Jesse Raphael Show" TV series in New York, NY.
  - Job Folder and Other Activities, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Includes Pima Council on Aging in Tucson, AZ; California State University Northridge in Northridge, CA; "Art of Darkness: A 'Night Gallery' Retrospective" DVD extra feature; "BUST Magazine" interview in Los Angeles, CA; "The Zingers" documentary in Los Angeles, CA.
  - Job Folders and Other Activities, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Includes Suncoast Hotel in Las Vegas, NV.
- Jokes and Gags, 1964-1988
  Includes jokes and gags by Diller, Gene Perrett and other writers hired by Diller, and joke writing services (in particular, Orben's joke writing service). Jokes cover a wide variety of topics. Documents were originally housed in binders, which were removed for preservation purposes, although Diller's organizational system has been maintained. Three of the original binders can be found in box 71.
  - Jokes and Gags, May-June 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    From binder titled: Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1963-1964, Book 1 (gags written by writers hired by Diller). Note: According to the original organization of the "Orange Set" binders, jokes go in reverse chronological order, with most recent first. Documents are sometimes slightly out of chronological order, as they were in Diller's original binders. (1 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, January-May 1964 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    From binder titled: Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1963-1964, Book 1. (2 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, January 1964 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    From binder titled: Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1963-1964, Book 1. (3 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, October-December 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    From binder titled: Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1963-1964, Book 1. (4 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, November-December 1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1964, Book 2. (1 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, October-November 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1964, Book 2. (2 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, September-October 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1964, Book 2. (3 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, July-September 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1964, Book 2. (4 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, May 1966-June 1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1965-1967, Book 3. Note: According to the original organization of the "Orange Set" binders, jokes go in reverse chronological order, with most recent first. (1 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, June 1965-May 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1965-1967, Book 3. (2 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, February-June 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1965-1967, Book 3. (3 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, January 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Writer's Gags, 1965-1967, Book 3. (4 of 4)
  - Jokes and Gags, November 1964-March 1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Phyllis' Gags, 1963-1966-68, Book 4. Note: Although this binder is labeled "Phyllis' gags," Folder 13 includes several pages of jokes and gags by Robert Orben. All jokes in the rest of Book 4 are by Diller. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, August 1964-November 1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Phyllis' Gags, 1963-1966-1968, Book 4. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, November 1963-July 1964 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Orange Set: Phyllis' Gags, 1963-1966-68, Book 4. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, August 1968-June 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Orange Set, Orben's Gags; Phyllis' Gags, Book 5." Folder includes jokes written by Orben. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, August 1968-June 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Orange Set, Orben's Gags; Phyllis' Gags, Book 5." Folder includes jokes written by Diller. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, April 1969-February 1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Orange Set, Writer's Gags, Book 6, 1965-1976." Folder includes jokes written by writers hired by Diller. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, December 1966-April 1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Orange Set, Writer's Gags, Book 6." Folder includes jokes written by writers hired by Diller. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, March 1965-December 1966 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Orange Set, Writer's Gags, Book 6." Folder includes jokes written by writers hired by Diller. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, January 1976-June 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags 1976-1986; Writer's Gags 1976- 1986…Travel books." This folder includes Diller's gags. Note: According to the original organization of the binder, jokes go in reverse chronological order, with most recent first. Not all months are represented. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, April 1979-July 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags 1976-1986; Writer's Gags 1976- 1986…Travel books." This folder includes gags by writers hired by Diller. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, April 1976-April 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags 1976-1986; Writer's Gags 1976- 1986…Travel books." This folder includes gags by writers hired by Diller. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, January 1976-October 1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags, 1976-1980; Writer's Gags, April '76-80." This folder includes gags written by Diller. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, April 1976-August 1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags, 1976-1980; Writer's Gags, April '76-80." This folder includes gags written by writers hired by Diller. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, March 1981-June 1987 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags and Writer Gags, 1981-1982, 1983- 1984, 1985-1986, 1988-1989." Folder includes jokes written by Diller. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, February 1981-January 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Phyllis Diller Gags and Writer Gags, 1981-1982, 1983- 1984, 1985-1986, 1988-1989." Folder includes jokes written by Diller. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, June-October 1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret Routines 1968." Includes jokes written for Diller by Perret. Includes index and list of joke topics. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, June-September 1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret Routines 1968." Includes jokes written for Diller by Perret. Includes index and list of joke topics. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, June-October 1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret All Gags Submitted I." Includes jokes written for Diller by Perret. Documents are mostly in reverse chronological order. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, June-August 1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret All Gags Submitted I." Includes jokes written for Diller by Perret. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: All Material Submitted II." Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. Although many of the documents are undated, the dates on some of the documents throughout the binder suggest that these were written in 1968 and 1969. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, Undated and 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: All Material Submitted II." Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. Although many of the documents are undated, the dates on some of the documents throughout the binder suggest that these were written in 1968 and 1969. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: All Material Submitted 1968-1969." Includes index (with a list of joke topics), and jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: All Material Submitted 1968-1969." Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: All Material Submitted 1968-1969." Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1970-72 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: New Material Submitted 1970-71-72." Includes index (with a list of joke topics), and jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: New Material Submitted 1970-71-72." Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1970-72 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret: New Material Submitted 1970-71-72." Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, January-April 1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret Gags/1982, Original Copies…" Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, May-August 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret Gags/1982, Original Copies…" Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, May-August 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    From binder titled "Gene Perret Gags/1982, Original Copies…" Includes jokes and gags written for Diller by Perret. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, August 1974-April 1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Orben Current Comedy, 1971-1976." Includes copies of "Orben's Current Comedy," a newsletter of jokes edited by Robert Orben and published by The Comedy Center, Inc. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, February 1971-August 1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Orben Current Comedy, 1971-1976." Includes copies of "Orben's Current Comedy," a newsletter of jokes edited by Robert Orben and published by The Comedy Center, Inc. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, June 1978-November 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    From binder titled "Orben Gags and Other Comedy Services, 1976-1980." Includes jokes from "Orben's Current Comedy" newsletter and other comedy services including Comedy/Update and O'Liners. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (1 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, April 1976-June 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    From binder titled "Orben Gags and Other Comedy Services, 1976-1980." Includes jokes from "Orben's Current Comedy" newsletter and other comedy services including Comedy/Update and O'Liners. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (2 of 2)
  - Jokes and Gags, May 1979-July 1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    From binder titled "Orben Gags & Other Comedy Services, 1976-1986…travel books." Includes jokes from "Orben's Current Comedy" newsletter and other comedy services including Comedy Today, Cheap Laughs, and O'Liners. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (1 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, May 1978-April 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    From binder titled "Orben Gags & Other Comedy Services, 1976-1986…travel books." Includes jokes from "Orben's Current Comedy" newsletter and other comedy services including Comedy Today, Cheap Laughs, and O'Liners. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (2 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, April 1976-May 1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    From binder titled "Orben Gags & Other Comedy Services, 1976-1986…travel books." Includes jokes from "Orben's Current Comedy" newsletter and other comedy services including Comedy Today, Cheap Laughs, and O'Liners. Documents are in reverse chronological order. (3 of 3)
  - Jokes and Gags, 1964-1988 (Box 71, Folder 1)